



# **ABOUT ME**

My background is in Art and Design which led me to work in the screen printing industry for many years. Now I'm starting on a new adventure in the web development field. I've always enjoyed challenges and troubleshooting so I knew I'd be a great programmer. I'm a fast learner that easily adapts to new situations. I'm Proficient in HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, and React.js., Node. js, Express and MySQL.



# **CONTACT**

813.391.1719

nickablack@gmail.com



# **SOCIAL MEDIA**

github.com/nblack0917 linkedin.com/in/nick-a-black



**SALES** 

# **EXPERIENCE**

HTML CSS **JAVASCRIPT** REACT.JS **EXPRESS.JS PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR DISC GOLF** 

# NICK BLACK

WEB DEVELOPER



#### **WORK HISTORY**

# Zollege

March 2021 - Present

Junior Web Developer: Collaborating with a small team to develop and deploy small applications for a non-profit sector of Zollege and Austin Coding Academy.

## River City Supply, LLC

January 2017 - March 2020

Sales associate and service specialist: Performed sales (counter, phone, and online), inventory and warehouse management, ordering, and customer service. Also a Mimaki certified wide-format printer service technician.

#### Fast Forward Ink

September 2014 - January 2017

Production Manager and Manual Screen Printer: Handled production, order management, fulfillment, art separations, and customer service for established screen printing business.



### **EDUCATION**

# Austin Coding Academy

September 2020 - March 2021

Full Stack Web Developer Certificate: Learned the most popular and common programming languages and how to build a site or app from idea to deployment.

### Ringling College of Art and Design

August 1999 - May 2003

Bachelors of Fine Arts majoring in Illustration: Learned multiple drawing, painting, and sculpting techniques from industry professionals. Graduated with High Honors.



## **CURRENT PROJECTS**

#### **REFERENCES**

# small-business-app

- · React.js
- · Maps game stores in the Austin area
- · https://stoic-turing-8467db.netlify.app

#### Garden-plan-ter

- · React.js, Express.js, MySQL
- · Garden Layout and Scheduling app
- · https://garden-plan-ter.netlify.app/

#### O Draftrr.com

- · React.js, Express.js, MySQL
- · First draft writing app
- · https://draftrr.com/

# Kevin Wilson

**Professional Reference** Owner - River City Supply, LLC kevin@ScreenPrintSupplies.com 512.454.0505

#### Matt Foster

Personal Reference matt.r.foster@gmail.com 972.786.4871



#### **HOBBIES**













- INTERESTING FACTS
- My artwork has been displayed in a gallery show that also featured Shepard Fairey's art
- I grew up next door to an actor from The Sopranos